m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯：紫杉 珞珞珞小娘 vitaminwater janiceyj 宏奇奇
翻譯：靜妹粒  持久君  王二川  衛管小色盲  欠斤夕四
時間軸：密斯恩  NO.Zero   后期：、青衣
校對：紫杉     總監：紫杉
這里是911  你有什么緊急情況
911 operator. What's your emergency?
我在天景旅館
I'm at the Sky View Motel.
我就是來送個東西  你們趕緊派人來
I was making a delivery. You have to send someone.
我覺得他們已經死了
I think they're dead.
-請慢一點  先生  -我不確定  但是...
- Slow down, sir. - I don't know for sure, but...
你先告訴我發生了什么事
You need to tell me what happened.
有人受傷了嗎
Are there people injured?
都是血  到處都是血
There's blood. There's blood everywhere.
這次的現場一塌糊涂
Well, it's a messy one.
要是不信  可以問問那個
If you don't believe me, ask the pizza
-送披薩的小伙子  -我知道
- delivery guy there. - Yeah, is he the one
-就是他報的警吧  -沒錯  他給這里一個房間
- who called it in? - Yeah, he was delivering pizzas
送披薩的外賣
to, uh, one of the rooms nearby.
114號房門半掩著  他就往里望了一眼
The door to 114 was ajar, so he looked in.
-現場怎樣  -兩名死者
- What do we have? - Two victims.
-史密斯夫婦  -真有創意[調侃已有電影《史密斯夫婦》]
- Mr. And Mrs. Smith. - Oh, that's original.
有人認識他們嗎
Anybody know who they really are?
沒有
No.
我也不明白他們到底作了什么孽
And I don't know what they did to deserve this.
...63... 64... 65...
66, 67...
68... 69... 70...
-71  72  -你在干嘛  大衛
- 71, 72... - Talk to me, David.
我想確定到底有多少處刺傷
I'm trying to determine the number of stab wounds.
說實話  實在是數不過來
But, frankly, there are just too many to count.
這場景真是令人惴惴
This is disturbing.
等等
Hey, wait a minute.
不是騙你們  我覺得我來過這兒
You know something? I've been here.
沒錯  之前我們也來這條街上處理過一起過量吸毒的案子
Yeah, we had that OD out on the street a while back.
也是在旅館里  但我是說這間房間
In the motel, but I mean, in this room-- this exact one.
我來過這兒
I-I've been here.
114號房間
Room 114.
我記得從這個窗戶看出去的霓虹燈
I remember the view of the neon from that window.
-就是這個  -沒錯
- This is it. - You're right.
我們來過這兒  是樁肢解案
We have been here before. Yeah, it was a
被害男性二十出頭的樣子
dismemberment murder; victim was in his 20s.It was about,
-大概是兩個月前  -不  我覺得是最近的事兒
- uh, two months ago. - No, I think it was more recent.
是另一對夫婦  妻子在睡夢中
It was another couple, but the woman was bludgeoned...
被襲擊那次
in her sleep.
我很確定是肢解那次
I am pretty sure it was the dismemberment.
抱歉打斷你們  可我覺得你們都是對的
I'm sorry, but-but you're both right.
我來過這兒兩次了
I've been here twice before,
第一次是肢解  然后是那對夫妻
once for the dismemberment and again for the couple.
現在是第三次
And now this.
不覺得這間房有股異樣的感覺嗎
Anybody else getting a really bad feeling about this place?
是啊  絕對是世界上最不詳的客房了
Yeah... yeah, this the world's most unlucky motel room.
《犯罪現場調查》  第十四季第九集
三起案子都發生在
All right, that's three murder scenes
同一個現場
all in the same spot.
肯定有聯系  你覺得呢
They got to be related, don't you think?
也許被害人之間有某些相通之處
Maybe there's a connection between the victims
又或者兇手有某種病態的偏好
or the killer has a weird fixation of some kind.
我暫時沒法回想之前的案子
I don't think I'm ready to talk about past crimes yet.
得先把精力放在這個上
Have to focus on this one first.
我明白
Yeah, I hear you.
我來處理浴室
I'll take the bathroom.
你管理這里多少時間
So, how long have you been manager here?
從我會走路時我就在管了
Uh, since about the time I learned to walk.
我父母造的這家賓館  我就在這兒長大的
My parents built this place, so... I grew up here.
現在都是我的了
All mine now.
你覺得誰比較可疑  可能是兇手
Do you have any idea who might've done this?
這不是你們的活嗎
Isn't that your business to figure that out?
雖然我們不是百樂宮[維加斯著名酒店賭場]  但是...
I mean, I know we're not the Bellagio, but...
如果我不得不還要因此降價
if I have to drop the rates any lower,
那我還不如把這地方封起來算了
I might as well just board the place up.
也是  所以你這里大概有二十間屋子
So, you got about, what, uh, 20 rooms here?
說說都什么樣的人住在這里
Tell me about the people who stay in them.
就跟價格牌上寫的那樣  有人過夜就走
It's like the sign says. I mean, by the night,
有人一待一周或者一個月
by the week and by the month.
我需要住客名單
I'm gonna need a list of names.
恐怕不行
Well, that could be a problem.
不是我不愿意給你  只是...
Not that I wouldn't give it, it's just...
我根本就沒有
I don't have it.
你也不看看這兒是什么地
Come on, man.
才三十九塊錢一晚
The place is 39 bucks a night.
只要有人給現金
If people have cash,
我又何必管他們叫什么
what do I care about their names?
他們不可能是兇手的  相信我
Look, none of 'em are killers, though-- trust me.
你又怎么知道他們不是
How do you know that?
因為他們都沒這個能耐
Well, there's no one here that interesting.
芬恩
Hey, Finn!
看起來史密斯夫婦昨晚有客人
Looks like the Smiths had a guest last night.
毛巾是潮的  我還在浴室下水道口
The towels are damp, and I found
找到一根紅頭發
a red hair in the shower drain.
那跟兩個被害者的都不一樣
Hmm, that doesn't match either of our victims.
而且水池邊上有三支牙刷
And there were three toothbrushes around the sink.
我找到了其中一支的收據
Uh, I found a receipt for one.
是昨晚在街角的藥店買的
It's from the drugstore around the corner-- last night.
所以是個不速之客
So a guest they didn't plan on.
還有別的  他們還買了洗發水
There's more. They also bought shampoo
和一把剪刀
and a pair of scissors,
剪刀已經不見了
which have since disappeared.
可能就是兇器
Could be the murder weapon.
所以在殺戮開始之前
So there was someone in here
有人在這里  對  那人洗了澡
before the killing started. Yeah, who showered
而且  我不明白  從牙刷來看
and-- I don't know-- judging from the toothbrush,
那人可能還打算在這里過夜
might've been planning on staying the night.
到底出了什么事兒呢
So what went wrong?
我干這行已經夠久了  沒什么能再讓我震驚的
I've been doing this long enough that nothing
如果一定要說有的話...
shocks me, but if a case could...
就是這案子里純粹的野蠻和殘暴
Just the sheer savagery involved.
每個受害者身上都有超過一百個傷口
More than a hundred stab wounds in each victim.
完全沒必要捅這么多下...
Certainly beyond what was necessary...
如果只是想殺了他們的話
if the goal was to simply kill them.
我能看看嗎
Can I see that?
這遠遠超出了我們平時看到的
It's, uh, way beyond what we sometimes see
因沖動或極度憤怒而犯罪的程度
with crimes of passion or extreme anger.
這是精神錯亂
This was madness.
他們真的姓史密斯
Their names really were Smith.
理查德和安
Richard and Ann.
據家人說  他們是從弗拉格斯塔夫[亞利桑那州]
According to family, they were in from Flagstaff
為一個古董玩具收集展而來的
for an antique toy and collectibles convention.
這可以解釋屋子里的玩偶們
That would explain the dolls in the room.
聽起來他們是正經人
Sounds like they were solid people.
她免費在一家養老院做寵物治療師
She volunteered, ran pet therapy at an old folks home.
他為流浪漢提供幫助
He worked with the homeless.
背景很清白
Squeaky clean.
當然  這也不是第一次清清白白的人
Course, that wouldn't be the first time the...
在拉斯維加斯放縱自己的陰暗面
squeaky-clean have indulged their dark side here in Vegas.
他們可能邀請某個人回了房間
They could've invited somebody back to the room,
為他們的生活增加一些樂趣
spice up their life a little bit.
如果是這樣...
If so...
他們得到的一定比想要的多
certainly got more than they bargained for.
我調出了...
Hey. So, I... pulled the files
另兩起旅館謀殺案的現場資料
for the other two motel murder scenes.
這很奇怪  你不覺得嗎
It's weird, don't you think?
一個兇手執著于一間屋子
That a killer would fixate on one room?
你覺得意義是什么呢
What do you think the significance is?
為什么他一定要在那里殺人呢
Why does he feel the need to kill there?
你是在假設
Well, that's assuming
這都是一個兇手做的案
that these are all the work of one killer.
也有可能這些案子沒有聯系
It could be that there's no connection.
你在尋找根本不存在的作案模式
That you're looking for patterns where there are none.
所以這只是三個完全不相干的兇手
So it's a coincidence that three totally unrelated killers
選了同一間屋子的巧合嗎
chose this one room?
我只是說  我們還不知道
I'm just saying, we don't know yet.
好吧
All right,
第一起是馬克·貝爾
first one Mark Bell.
十一周之前  在他女朋友
11 weeks ago, he stayed
把他趕出家門之后他住在114號房
in Room 114 after his girlfriend kicked him out.
對  我記得  我和芬恩辦的這個案子
Yeah, I remember. I worked this case with Finn.
服務員發現他被綁在床上
The maid found him tied to the bed,
十一周前
腿被嚴重劃傷  差不多都切斷了
severe lacerations to his legs. They were nearly cut off.
他生生地流血過多而死
He bled to death.
地板上有一把帶血的刀
There was a bloody knife found on the floor.
血污太嚴重沒法找到有用的指紋
Too smeared to yield any viable prints.
那時候警探們認為
Detectives, at the time,
那次襲擊跟毒品債務有關
thought the attack was related to a drug debt.
他們認為毒販子在傳達某種信息
They thought the dealer was sending a message.
四周前...
Four weeks ago...
屋子里的第二起襲擊
second attack in the room.
艾利克斯和蒂娜·加內茲夫婦倆
Alex and Tina Garnez.
我和尼克處理的這個案子
Nick and I handled this one.
他們的房子被收去抵債了
Their house had been foreclosed on.
四周前
他們在車里住了好幾個月
They were living in their car for months.
加內茲先生終于找到了工作
Mr. Garnez finally got a job.
搬到汽車旅館也算是生活終于有了起色
Moving to the motel was supposed to be a step up.
那天晚上  他在廁所偷偷抽煙
That night, he was sneaking a cigarette in the bathroom
當時他妻子在睡覺
while his wife slept.
兇手先殺了他妻子
The killer started with his wife...
趁她睡著了  打死了她
...clubbing her while she was sleeping.
他一定是突然發現了加內茲先生居然在廁所里
Then he must've surprised Mr. Garnez in the bathroom...
于是也對他下了毒手
Overpowered him.
但他活下來了
He survived.
現在仍在醫院接受治療
He's still in the hospital recovering.
接著是昨晚
Then last night...
史密斯夫婦
the Smiths.
還覺得這些案子
Still think we're...
只是偶然  沒有任何聯系嗎
dealing with random, unrelated events?
好吧  芬恩
All right, Finn,
回頭到實驗室再見
I'll see you back at the lab.
出來吧  把門打開  我知道你在里面
Come on now. Open up. I saw you in there.
我昨晚睡著了
I was asleep last night.
跟我沒關系  我已經都告訴警察了
I was not involved. I already told the cops.
好好  沒事  我不是...
Oh, yeah, yeah. That's cool. I'm not, uh...
我不是來拷問你的
I'm not here to grill you.
看起來這個地方就是你的家啊
Kind of looks like you like to call this place home.
我猜附近的事你無所不知吧
I'm guessing you see everything that goes on in here.
你沒見到什么奇怪的事嗎
You...didn't see anything weird?
最近有沒有什么可疑的人出沒
Anybody suspicious running around here lately?
我沒資格去評價他人的人品
It's not my place to judge another man in that way.
只有上帝有資格
Only God can judge.
那好吧  上帝也會希望你
Right...well, God would want you
幫我找到殺人兇手  不是嗎
to help me catch a killer, wouldn't he?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
先生  拜托  拜托  聽我說
Sir, please, please, hey, come on, now.
昨晚一對夫妻被殘忍地殺害了
A couple was violently murdered last night.
幾個星期前是一位女士
A woman a few weeks ago.
在那之前是一位年輕小伙
A young man before that.
全在同一個屋里  他們都是無辜的
All in the same room, all innocent victims.
無辜  這世界上沒有誰是無辜的
Innocent? There's no one on this planet who's innocent.
我們都是罪人
We're all sinners.
好吧  不過
Yeah, yeah, well, that-that
這跟我的工作無關
doesn't really help me do my job.
上帝把他們召回了
They were called to God.
這是上帝的計劃
That's God's plan.
你的任務已經完成了
Your job is done.
我只是...
Yeah, I just...
最讓我后悔從事現場調查這個工作的事兒
Might be my biggest regret about this job --
大概就是因此而知酒店被單有多臟了
I know way too much about hotel bedspreads.
酒店地毯也是  一定不要光腳進門
And hotel carpets. Don't go barefoot.
這里是三個不同犯罪現場的
So, we have three different bedspreads from our...
三床不同的被單
three different crime scenes.
我查了DNA
I ran the DNA.
最左邊的被單來自
The bedspread on the left is
第一個犯罪現場
from the very first murder scene.
我敢說這床被單一定在那屋里很長時間了
I'm guessing it lived in that room for who knows how long.
長得我都能從上面找出
Long enough that I was able to identify
二十六組不同的DNA
26 individual DNA profiles.
替代了這床的被單只在這間房里
The replacement bedspread there was only in the room
-呆了七周  -所以DNA少一些
- for seven weeks. - So fewer contributions.
只有十六組
16 of them.
來自昨晚的犯罪現場的第三床被單
And the third bedspread, from last night's crime scene.
只有九組不同的DNA
Yielded only nine contributors.
可是問題是  三床被單上
But here's the thing: one of them, a male,
都有同一位男性的DNA
is common to all three bedspreads.
同一個人  在三起兇殺案發生前
One person, the same person was in the room
這人都進過那件屋
before each of the murders?
你有在DNA索引系統上查到匹配嗎
Have you run the samples through CODIS?
現在正在檢索
It's running right now.
查到了
Here we go.
蘭德爾·威克斯  二十二歲  他的信息
Randall Wicks, 22. He must have
一定是剛剛才被加進系統
just been added to the system.
他兩周前被控性侵及毆打罪
There's why -- sexual battery charge two weeks ago.
瞧他在哪里被逮捕的
Look where he was arrested.
天景旅館  114房
同一家旅館  同一間房間
That same motel. The same room!
我給布拉斯打個電話
I'll call Brass,
叫他發出通緝
get out a broadcast.
英雄也會失勢啊  對吧  蘭德爾
Oh, how the mighty have fallen, huh, Randall?
你曾經是丹吉爾賭場的男侍夜總會的
You used to be the featured dancer in the Tangiers
首席舞者
All Male Review.
你怎么會把那個工作弄丟了呢
How'd you let that gig slip away?
我不知道
I don't know.
覺得無聊  就辭職了
I got bored, so I quit.
或許你找到了更有意思的活呢
Oh, well, maybe you found something more interesting to do, huh?
-搞什么啊  -在天景旅館的同一間屋里
- Oh, hey, man, what the hell? - Three separate murders
發生了三件兇殺案
in the same room at the Sky View Motel.
每起案件發生后
Your DNA was found in the room
你的DNA都會出現在那個房間
after each of the crimes.
什么  等等  你是說天景旅館嗎
What? Wait a minute-- Sky View Motel?
是那個114號房間嗎
Was that in room 114?
我經常用那個房間
I use that room, frequently.
有業務在身
For business.
這么說  你是牛郎
So... you're a prostitute?
伙計  我可是匹種馬
Dude, I'm a stud,
我是讓那些沮喪的家庭主婦嘗嘗
letting frustrated housewives get a taste of something
她們原本想都別想的好滋味
they wouldn't even get close to otherwise.
行了  種馬  在114號房
Okay, stud, what about
被你打的那個家庭主婦是怎么回事
the housewife you beat up in room 114?
你不是被指控性侵犯嗎
The sexual battery charge.
還是說你們正玩騎馬[性交姿勢]呢
Or was that just part of the pony ride experience?
我那是自衛
That was self-defense.
真的
I'm serious.
我是為了保命
I was in fear for my life.
好吧
Okay...
我跟那女的約在那兒見面
I meet this woman there, right?
一開始很正常
Totally normal at first.
正當我們漸入佳境的時候
Then we start getting into it, and...
不知怎么  她突然發起瘋來
I don't know, she goes all crazy.
像是產生幻覺一樣
Starts hallucinating or something,
對著墻大喊大叫
screaming at the walls.
-太恐怖了  -怎么回事
- Pure freak show. - And why?
是什么引起的
What would make her do that?
我又不是醫生  不過...
Well, I ain't a doctor or nothing, but...
肯定是我的床上功夫把她震撼了
must be the sex just blew her mind.
那是  肯定是這么回事
Yeah, that must have been it.
就是個廢物  你還有其他想法嗎
Well... aside from being a complete tool, what do you think?
他是兇手的可能性還是有的
Well, he still could be our killer.
問題是  我們只掌握了DNA
Well, the problem is, all we have is DNA evidence,
他說了他的DNA怎么會在那個房間的
and we can't disprove his story
我們沒法推翻這種說法
of how it got in that room.
不過我們有個目擊證人  可以指認蘭德爾
Well, we do have an eyewitness who could possibly I.D. Randall.
艾利克斯·加內茲  四周前他妻子被打死了
Alex Garnez, the husband who survived his wife being bludgeoned
他活了下來
four weeks ago.
他有嚴重的顱腦損傷
He has massive head injuries.
他還在醫院呢
He's still in the hospital--
都不知道他現在什么情況
we don't even know what condition he's in.
我找過他的醫生了
Well, I talked to his doctor.
她說他心理狀況不佳
She said he's struggling psychologically.
自從他有次自殺未遂  他們就一直看著他
They have him on suicide watch after one failed attempt,
不過從生理上來說
but... physically...
他已經恢復了  我們可以去問話
she said he's strong enough to talk to us.
加內茲先生
Mr. Garnez.
我是犯罪現場調查員布洛迪
I'm CSI Brody,
這位是犯罪現場調查員桑德斯
and this is CSI Sanders.
不好意思  我們得跟你談談
I'm sorry, but we need to talk to you
有關你和你妻子遇襲那晚的事
about the night that you and your wife were attacked.
你還記得多少
How much do you remember?
我不知道
I don't know.
我…我…
I... I...
我記得她就躺在那兒
I remember her just lying there,
就那樣躺著
just lying there.
身上周圍都是血
And all the... blood around her...
我們是高中情侶
We were high school sweethearts.
你有沒有看見傷害你和你妻子的人
Did you see the person who hurt you and your wife?
記得他的長相嗎
Do you remember his face?
我能看見他
I can see him...
站在她身旁
standing over her,
一直打她
hitting her over...
and over...
可是...
and...
可是我無能為力
and I'm powerless.
我沒法制止他
I... I can't stop him.
就像我們之間隔著一堵墻一樣
Like there's a wall between us. I...
可我還是能聽到那恐怖的聲音
Yet I can still hear the sickening sound of...
一下
blow...
又一下
after blow.
加內茲先生
Mr. Garnez...
我們想給你看幾張照片
we want to... we want to show you some photographs
是人像照
of some faces.
請你告訴我們其中哪個
We need you to tell us if any one of these men
像是你剛剛說的那個人
looks like the man that we've been talking about, okay?
不在這里面
He's not there.
你確定嗎
Are you sure?
這些人...
None of these...
都不是殺害我家蒂娜的人
is the man that killed my Tina.
霍奇斯  你給我發了條"911"
Hodges, you texted me "911"?
沒錯
I did.
什么事兒這么急
What is the 911?
抱歉  是你的嫌犯
Sorry. Your suspect.
他光著腳從汽車旅館跑出來  對吧
He ran from the motel room barefoot, correct?
但是他的鞋沒留下
Yet he left no shoes behind.
有可能他拿走了
He could have been carrying his shoes.
他來不及穿上它們了
He was in too much of a hurry to put them on.
也許吧  但是尼克在浴室
Mm, maybe. But there was a bottle of shampoo
找到了瓶洗發水
that Nick found in the bathroom.
它含有1%的芐氯菊酯
It contained one percent permethrin,
是去虱的配方
formulated to combat head lice.
我已經和醫生確認過了
Now, I've checked with Doc.
史密斯夫婦倆誰都沒有頭虱
Neither of the Smiths were head lice sufferers.
這么說洗發水是給客人準備的
So the shampoo was for the guest.
沒錯  很有可能就是兇手
Yes. Presumably the killer.
尼克在淋浴間的墻上發現了殘留物
Nick found residue on the wall of the shower.
我檢測過了  它含有5%的芐氯菊酯
I've tested it; it contained five percent permethrin.
-芐氯菊酯  治頭虱的  -不是
- Permethrin, for the head lice. - No.
它的含量是5%  在沐浴乳里
This is five percent, in a body cream.
這是處方藥的劑量  用來治療疥瘡
It's prescription strength, used to treat scabies.
我不想表現得不近人情  但是…
I don't want to seem insensitive, but...
不穿鞋  頭虱
shoeless, head lice,
還有疥瘡  我覺得他是個流浪漢
and scabies-- that all sounds like homeless to me.
理查德·史密斯在弗拉格斯塔夫
Richard Smith worked with the homeless
幫助流浪漢
back in Flagstaff.
他可能是想救濟他
He could have been doing
想幫助某個流浪漢
some sort of outreach, wanted to help somebody,
從街上把他們帶回來
brought them in off the street.
我已經打聽過了
I've already called around.
那邊有個收容所叫"街道救星"
There's a local shelter called Street Saviors
上周爆發了一場疥瘡
who had a scabies outbreak last week,
他們發的正是同樣的處方沐浴乳
where they distributed this very same prescription cream.
太棒了  霍奇斯
Way to bury the lead, Hodges.
這不過是蒼海一瓢
That's part of my charm.
哥就是個傳說
It's all in the telling.
老樣子
The regular.
對  水果味的
Yeah. Fruity.
好  非常感謝
Okay, thanks so much.
我和一對從事
Hey. So I talked to a couple
救濟工作的夫妻談過了
of the outreach workers.
他們之前見過一個人  他叫魯迪
They saw a guy earlier, a guy named Rudy.
他是這兒的常客了
He's a regular here.
他光著腳  衣服上有血跡
He was barefoot, had bloodstained clothes.
聽起來像我們要找的人
Sounds like our boy.
沒錯  據當地的居民說
Yeah. According to the locals,
他喜歡在這邊閑逛  就在橋底下
he likes to hang out here, under the bridge.
有人看見魯迪了嗎
Anybody seen Rudy?
你看見魯迪了嗎
You seen Rudy?
你認識魯迪嗎
You know who Rudy is?
魯迪在哪兒呢
Hey, where does Rudy stay?
老前輩  您好
Hey, old-timer. Hey, man.
看見魯迪在哪兒了嗎
You seen Rudy anywhere?
魯迪
Rudy!
怎么了
What's wrong?
你都干了什么啊  老兄
What have you been doing, man?
魯迪  你得跟我們走一趟
Rudy, you're gonna have to come with us.
魯迪  你的檔案里提到
Rudy, it says here in my files
你在州立醫院住過一段時間
that you spent some time in the state hospital.
因為精神問題嗎
Had a few psych holds?
是  我是有些問題
Yeah, I have some problems.
你的醫生說你是什么病
What did the doctors diagnose you with?
精神分裂癥  躁郁癥
Schizophrenia, bipolar disorder,
廣泛性焦慮癥
generalized anxiety,
-妄想癥  -夠了
- paranoia... - Well, that's okay.
我們明白了
We get the idea.
你認識這兩個人嗎  理查德和安
Do you recognize these two? Richard and Ann?
他們是天使
They're angels.
-你什么意思  -他們救了我
- What do you mean? - They rescued me.
-怎么救的  -我在街上  在克雷默街
- How? - I was on the street, out front
一家藥店前
of a drugstore on Cramer.
那就在天景旅館附近
Oh, that's right near the Sky View Motel.
有時候我去那兒去換零錢  然后我...
I go there sometimes to ask for change, you know, and-and I...
那些人
These guys,
他們搶我錢  還…還…
they jumped me and-and...
還打我
and they beat me,
然后他們拿走了我的零錢和鞋子
and they took my change and they took my shoes.
如果不是理查德和安
And-and it probably would have been worse,
從天而降
except that Richard and Ann came along
趕走了他們
out of nowhere and...
情況可能會更糟
and chased them away.
魯迪  后來發生了什么
Rudy, what happened next?
我告訴過你們了  他們是天使
I told you, they're angels.
他們  他們...
They-they-they...
他們問我是否想留在他們的房間
they asked me if I wanted to stay in their room with them,
還給我買了牙刷和其他的東西
and they got me a toothbrush and stuff,
他們讓我洗個澡  清洗一下
and they let me get a shower and get all cleaned up.
洗完澡后發生了什么
Did something happen after the shower?
發生了一些事情  不是嗎
Something happened, didn't it?
我不記得了
I don't remember.
得了吧  魯迪  想想
Come on, Rudy, think.
用力想想
Think real hard.
不  不
No! No!
有很多娃娃...
There were these dolls...
而且很多很多
a-and there were a whole bunch of them,
它們開始跟我說話  它們都看著我
and they started talking to me and they were looking at me.
它們在說些什么  魯迪
What were they saying, Rudy?
他們說了什么
What did they say?
是娃娃們讓你這么做的嗎
Did the dolls tell you to do this?
我...
I...
是我干的  不是嗎  我用剪刀干的
I did that, didn't I? I did that with the scissors.
我傷害了他們
I hurt them.
那這些人呢
What about these people?
你是不是也傷害了他們呢
Did you hurt them, too?
我不知道
I don't know.
有時候我會想
You know, sometimes I think we forget
我們都忘了人類是既脆弱又復雜的機器
what delicate, complex machines we are.
只要一些神經突觸傳輸不暢
You know, all it takes are a few short-circuiting synapses,
或者髓鞘斷裂[均為精神疾病可能的生理原因]
or a breakdown in myelination,
一切就運轉失常了
and everything gets thrown out of whack.
朱爾斯  你剛抓住了一個兇手
Jules, you just captured a killer.
我知道  但我為什么感覺很不好呢
I know. Then why do I feel so bad?
因為他看上去是個好人
Because he seems like a nice guy
卻無奈命運不公
who got dealt a lousy hand in life.
所以是他殺了史密斯夫婦的  對嗎
So we have him for killing the Smiths, right?
那之前兩次襲擊呢
What about the other two attacks?
我可以仔細檢查所有的證據  提出論據
Well, I could go over all the evidence and make a case.
他明顯是我們的首要嫌疑犯
He's obviously our prime suspect.
他經常出現在那個區域
He frequented the area,
而且他明顯很不穩定
and he's obviously unstable.
做得好
Good work.
你花了很多時間在這個案子上
You put some long hours in on this.
為什么不回個家
Why-why don't you go home,
休息一下呢
get yourself some rest.
一周后
冷靜  冷靜點
Take it, take it easy!
一加一等于二  一個給我一個給你
One plus one is two. One for me and one for you.
二加二等于四
Two plus two is four.
還有更多的  三加三等于六
That's a couple more. Three plus three is six.
直棍和曲棍
Straight and crooked sticks!
走開
Get away!
一加一等于二
One plus one is two.
一個給我一個給你
One for me and one for you.
二加二等于四  還有更多的
Two plus two is four, and that's a couple more.
一加一等于二  一個給我一個給你
One plus one is two. One for me and one for you.
二加二等于四  還有更多的
Two plus two is four. That's a couple more.
-三加三等于六  -女士
- Three plus three is six. - Ma'am.
直棍和曲棍
Straight and crooked sticks.
放下那個瓶子  聽到了嗎
You need to drop that bottle, do you hear me?
四加四等于八  海鷗在門上
Four plus four is eight. Seagulls on the gate!
五加五等于十
Five plus five is ten.
你聽到我說的了嗎
Do you hear what I'm saying?!
放下瓶子
Drop the bottle!
里奇就是不聽指令
Ricky doesn't follow directions!
他從來都不聽從指令
He never follows directions!
謝謝你  兄弟
Thanks, man.
鄭重表示感謝
Seriously, thanks.
-謝謝  -沒關系
- Thanks. - All right.
她住在這嗎  就這家旅館嗎
Was she staying here? In the motel?
是的  今晚入住的
Uh, yeah, just since tonight.
哪間房
What room?
又來了
It's happened again.
到底怎么回事
How the hell can this be?
我以為我們抓到兇手了
I thought we had our killer.
是我們搞錯了嗎  朱爾斯
Did we mess up, Jules?
錯怪那個流浪漢了嗎
Did we make a mistake with our-our homeless guy?
不  魯迪是有罪的  也許另兩件案子不是他
No, Rudy's guilty, maybe not of all three,
但肯定是他殺的史密斯夫婦
but he definitely killed the Smiths.
那我們怎么解釋這個
Then how do we explain this?
我不知道
I don't know.
這可能...沒有關聯
It has to be... unrelated.
沒有關聯嗎
Unrelated?
過去三個月在同一間房里
Four murders in the same room
發生了四起謀殺
over a three-month period.
那肯定是有關聯的  你不覺得嗎
That's got to be connected, don't you think?
好吧  很抱歉
All right, I'm sorry.
今晚的主角又是是誰
Look, all right, who are our players tonight?
誰殺了誰
Who are we talking about here?
嫌疑人是名女性
Suspect is a woman,
二十八歲的高中數學教師
28-year-old high school math teacher.
受害者是她的一名學生
Victim was one of her students.
一同待在三十九塊錢一晚的臟兮兮的旅館
Together in a sleazy, $39-a-night motel room.
還有這些內衣  避孕套  性玩具和酒
With lingerie, condoms, sex toys and alcohol.
很好奇在這里發生了什么  對吧
Wonder what was going on here, right?
根據學校的網站顯示
Yeah, according to the school website,
她才剛剛被評為年度最佳教師
she was just named Teacher of the Year.
真是當之無愧
I'll bet she was.
這聽起來也許很瘋狂
So, this may sound crazy,
但是我覺得事情并不是像看起來那樣的
but I'm thinking that this isn't what it looks like.
我可不信這老師睡了她學生
I don't believe that the teacher was sleeping with her student.
沒錯  你是對的  是很瘋狂
Yeah, you're right, that sounds crazy.
聽聽我在她手機上找到的語音留言
Well, listen to this voice mail I found on her phone.
斯通老師  我是馬修
Ms. Stone, it's Matthew.
我不知道該怎么辦了
I don't know what to do,
我父母喝醉了在打架
but my parents have been drinking and fighting,
我回不了家
and I can't go home;
我在一家旅館
I'm at a motel.
但是我很害怕
But I'm scared.
我也不知道還能打給誰
I don't know who else to call.
很抱歉  但是你得幫幫我  拜托了
I'm sorry, but you have to help me, please.
斯通老師  我們很想弄明白
Ms. Stone, we are trying to make sense
在那房間里發生了什么
out of what happened in that room.
但是我們需要你的幫助
But we need your help to do that.
小男生馬修一定跟你說了很悲慘的故事
Boy Matthew must have told you a really sad story
才把你誘騙到那家旅館吧
to lure you to that motel room.
很顯然  從他帶的那些東西就能看出
Now, obviously, from the items he brought along,
他想跟你發生點什么
he had ideas of getting romantic with you.
房間里還有很多空酒瓶
Now, there were a lot of empty liquor bottles in the room.
他當時喝醉了嗎
Was the young man drunk?
他一點酒也沒喝
There wasn't any drinking.
我一到那兒就把所有酒都倒洗手池里了
First thing I did was dump all the alcohol down the sink.
我想讓馬修清楚什么也不會發生
I wanted it clear to Matthew that nothing was going to happen.
他失控了嗎
Did he get upset?
是那時他開始脅迫你的嗎
Is that when he threatened you?
他永遠不會那么做的
He would never.
馬修是個...馬修是個很好的孩子
Matthew's a... Matthew's a great kid.
他只不過失手敲碎了一個瓶子
He just had a harmless crush, that's all.
他永遠不會傷害我的
He would never hurt me.
那你為什么殺了她
Then why did you kill him?
不是我干的
It wasn't me.
真的嗎  不是你嗎
Really? Wasn't you?
斯通老師  看  看這個
Ms. Stone, look, look at this.
那不是我
That's not me.
這是我  是我的身體  但是我...
I mean, it's me, it's my body, but I...
我無法控制自己
I had no control.
就好像被什么附身了一樣
It was like there was something inside me.
我當時
I was...
著魔了...
...possessed.
你當時怎么了
You were what?
著魔了...
...possessed.
我也不知道  我還真有點想要相信她
I don't know. Part of me really wants to believe her.
昨晚視頻里咆哮尖叫的女人
I mean, the woman ranting and screaming on that video
跟今天我看到的她完全不一樣
from last night was nothing like the woman I met today.
她們完全就是兩個人
They were two totally different people.
所以她昨晚的行為是完全反常的
So, her behavior last night was completely out of character.
醫院做了毒檢嗎
Did the hospital do a tox screen?
做了  她是干凈的  甚至連一點酒精都沒有
Yeah, it was clean. Not even alcohol.
那肯定是那房間了
Then it's got to be the room.
房間讓她那么做的
The room made her do it.
像《閃靈》里面[史蒂芬·金小說  后改編成電影]
What, like, The Shining?
"遠眺酒店"一樣嗎[《閃靈》故事發生的酒店]
The Overlook Hotel?
這是聯系所有這些謀殺的事物
It's the one thing connecting all of the murders.
而且現在也是唯一的
Right now, it's the only thing.
好吧  那我們讓霍奇斯和亨利把儀器弄過去
Okay, so, let's have Hodges and Henry drag their equipment out there
檢查下那間房  看他們怎么說吧
and test the room, see what they have to say.
我在空調里檢測到了一些高揮發性有機物
I've got some elevated VOCs in the air conditioner,
但都不能解釋那些奇怪的行為中的任何一種
but nothing that would explain any of the bizarre behavior.
你那邊呢
What about you?
發現什么了嗎
You got anything yet?
能給我幾分鐘先看看嗎
Could I have five minutes to look first?
我可真喜歡這臟死了的衛生間
Oh, and I'm very much enjoying the dirty bathroom.
謝謝你
Thank you for that.
很好  今天我肯定渾身水果味了
Great. Now I can smell like a fruit bowl for the rest of the day.
壁櫥的內壁上好像發霉了
It looks like they've got mold inside the walls of the closet.
我會取個樣
I'm going to have to get a sample.
你那兒有撬桿嗎
Do you have the pry bar in there?
我要撬開石膏板
Hey, I have to open some drywall.
你工具箱里面有撬桿嗎
Do you have the pry bar in your kit?
霍奇斯
Hodges!
玩我呢
Seriously?
霍奇斯  你在干嘛
Hodges, what are you doing?
我叫你呢
I was calling you.
你在看什么
What are you looking at?
怎么...你怎么了
What, what's going on with you?
我知道你是誰
I know who you are.
好吧  要不要在馬桶上坐會兒
Okay, look, w-why don't you have a seat on the toilet...
我來帶你出去  來
I'm gonna help you out, come here.
我知道你是個什么東西
I can see what you are!
霍奇斯  放開我  疼死了
Hodges, let go of me! That hurts!
不要  霍奇斯
No... Hodges!
不  不
No, no...!
我是亨利·安德魯斯
This is Henry Andrews.
我現在在天景旅館114號房
I'm at the Sky View Motel, room 114,
有緊急情況
and I have an emergency.
請馬上派警員和醫護人員過來
I need police and EMS immediately.
-請讓一讓  -亨利
- Excuse me... - Hey! Henry!
亨利
Henry?
哥們  你還好嗎
Hey, man, you all right?
這兒發生什么事了
What's going on out here?
我也不太清楚
I don't know exactly.
他突然發瘋
He just flipped out.
尼克  老實說我真的覺得他要殺了我
Nick, I honestly think he would have killed me.
-霍奇斯  -對  但又不是霍奇斯
- Hodges? - Yeah, but it wasn't Hodges.
我是說  如果你當時有看到他的眼神
I mean, if you would've seen the look in his eyes,
他在里面一定發生了什么
something must have happened to him in there,
發生了使他變成這樣的事情
something to trigger this.
-他和你說了什么  -什么都沒說
- What'd he say to you? - Nothing.
他的話完全不知所云
Everything that came out of him was unintelligible.
只有咕噥聲和咆哮聲
It was grunts and growls.
醫護人員給他注射了鎮定劑
Hey, so paramedics hit him with a sedative.
一旦他們把他帶到了醫院
Once they get him to the hospital,
我們或許就會知道發生了什么
maybe we'll figure out what's going on.
等  等下  帶走他之前  我需要根棉簽
Wait, wait, before he goes, I-I need a-a... a swab.
背心里說不定有
Check your vest.
停一下
Hold up.
哥們
Hey, buddy,
我需要取點唾液樣本
I just need to get some saliva.
你能幫我嗎
Can you help me out?
你能張開嘴嗎
Can you open up?
來  張開嘴
Come on, just open up.
這就對了  配合我一下
There you go, help me out.
很好
Good.
帶他離開這吧
Yeah, get him out of here.
生命體征正常...
Vitals are good...
-謝謝  醫生  我很感激  -不客氣
- Thanks, Doc. I appreciate it. - You're welcome.
他有說什么嗎  他怎么樣了
What did he say? How's he doing?
他會好起來的
He's gonna be okay.
他的生命體征都在正常范圍
I mean, his vitals are all in the normal range.
也不像有什么身體不適
He doesn't seem to be in any physical distress.
顯然那間汽車旅館的房間有問題
Well, obviously there is something going on in that motel room.
現在霍奇斯也成了在那間房里
Now we need to add Hodges to the list
發瘋的一員了  對吧
of people that went nuts in there, right?
流浪漢  老師
Homeless guy, the teacher--
讓我對第一位死者好奇起來  馬克·貝爾
Makes me wonder about our first victim, Mark Bell.
說不定他也是發了瘋
Who's to say he didn't go crazy, too,
狠狠地切了自己的腿
and stab himself in his legs.
如果這些都是真的
If all of this is true,
那個痛失愛妻的人  又怎么說呢
what's it say about the man who lost his wife?
各位
Hey, guys,
你們一定不會相信的
you are not gonna believe this one.
霍奇斯被下藥了
Hodges was drugged.
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
迷幻藥  我用他的唾液做了酶聯測試
LSD-- I did an ELISA test on his saliva.
方式未知  但一定是
Somehow, he must've been dosed
我們在房間里工作的時候給下藥了
while we were in the room working.
等下  醫院不是給老師和魯迪都做了
Wait a minute, didn't the hospital do a tox screen
毒理檢測嗎  檢測結果不是陰性嗎
on the teacher and on Rudy, and it came back negative?
常規毒檢是不會檢測迷幻藥的
The standard tox panel doesn't test for LSD,
所以他們很可能也被下藥了
so they were probably dosed, too--
只是我們無從得知
we just had no way to know it.
但是為什么會有暴力行為
But wh-why the violence?
我發現的分子中混合了很多雜質
The molecules I found were highly adulterated,
混有類似五氯酚的苯甲嗪
and cut with a cyclidine similar to PCP.
可能來自于某個廚房洗滌槽
Probably came out of somebody's kitchen sink.
好的
Okay.
現在我們知道了有致幻物
Now we know what.
去弄清楚它如何到受害者體內的吧
Let's go find out how.
根據亨利所說  這種迷幻藥會發藍光
So, according to Henry, this lysergic acid glows blue.
而且藥效很強
And the stuff's potent.
我們要找的也許就是一點點痕跡
We may not be looking for much.
等等  這兒有發現
Wait a minute-- got something over here.
極小的液滴滴
These are tiny drops.
像是噴出來的
It looks like they might've been aerosolized.
看看  發藍光的液體
Check it out-- covered in blue.
原來就在這兒
This is our source right here.
如果霍奇斯被它噴中的話
If Hodges got sprayed by that,
只可能噴在他的嘴唇或眼睛上
it would only have to land on his lips or in his eye,
然后被迅速吸收
and it would be instantly absorbed.
這兒  讓我裝進袋里
Here, let me bag it.
等等
Hold on here.
我不認為致幻劑來自那只噴筒
I don't think the LSD was coming from that cartridge.
這里有只軟管
There's a hose in here.
沒錯  它是從隔壁房間的墻壁穿過來
Yeah, and it's coming through the wall from the next room.
奧斯卡  能借用下你的衛生間嗎
Hey, Oscar, can we use your bathroom for a second?
你們可不能就這么闖進來
Hey! You can't come in here like this!
當然可以  仔細檢查  格雷格
Sure we can. Check it out, Greg.
相當理由: 合理確信犯罪嫌疑
這叫"相當理由"  奧斯卡
It's called probable cause, Oscar.
你發現了什么
What do you got?
我找到了噴劑的源頭
Found the source.
奧斯卡  我還記得我曾站在那兒
Oscar, I remember standing right there
聽你跟我扯上帝的意愿
and listening to you preach to me about God's will.
你所說的就是這個嗎
Is this what you meant? Huh?
殺死六個人
Killing six people?
我可沒殺任何人
I didn't kill anyone.
你一直在向隔壁的衛生間噴灑致幻劑
You've been spraying LSD all over the bathroom next door.
你該為他們的死負責
You're responsible!
我不知道你在說什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
上帝知道真相
God sees the truth.
-是啊  -上帝知道我是清白的
- Yes, sir! - God knows my heart!
你知道嗎  我不想再聽你扯什么上帝
You know what? I'm tired of hearing that.
給我坐下  我會親自送你去警察局
Sit down, relax. I'm gonna get you a ride.
尼克  看看這個
Nick, take a look at this.
把電視放在衣柜里也太詭異了
That's an odd place for a TV.
是隔壁房間  114號房
That's the room next door-- room 114.
所以不僅給隔壁旅客下藥
So not only have you been dosing the people next door,
你還全程錄下來了嗎
you've been recording it, too?
尼克  我找不到任何錄像設備
Hey, Nick, I don't see any recording device.
但這里裝有發射機
But there's this transmitter
向別處發射信號
set up to send a signal someplace else.
-那這里的錄像是怎么回事  -不知道
- So what's with all the video stuff? - I don't know.
我只知道我不能碰它
I just know I'm not supposed to touch it.
是嗎  誰跟你這么說的
Yeah? Who told you that?
特倫特  旅館經理
Trent, the manager.
他說如果我敢動  他就趕我出去
He said if I did, he'd kick me out.
特倫特·雷格  拿好拘捕令  警察局見
Trent Raeger, got a warrant. See you downtown.
尼克
Hey, Nick,
你快過來看看這個
you gotta come and see this.
這個偷窺狂在偷窺所有房間
Our peeper has been looking at all the rooms,
不只是114號房
not just room 114.
沒錯  他一直在這享受偷窺的樂趣
Yeah, he's been spending some quality time in here.
這些紀念物...
Hmm. These are all souvenirs...
全是從他喜愛的旅客那里偷來的
from his favorite guests.
你已經偷窺114號房很久了
You've been peeping on room 114 for a long time,
是不是  特倫特
haven't you, Trent?
何時起你決定不再只當一名偷窺狂
At what point did you decide that it wasn't enough to just be a voyeur?
我的意思是  何時起你決定殺人
I mean, when did you decide that you needed to kill people?
不是那樣的
It isn't like that.
好吧  那你告訴我究竟是怎樣
Okay, then tell me what it's like.
那只是...
Well, it's just about...
觀察  你知道嗎
watching, you know?
所有入住旅館的旅客
All the people coming through the motel.
在我小時候  我們一家人很想出外旅行
When I was a kid, we'd get a family on vacation,
我很好奇因為我們從未外出度假過
and I was curious because we never took vacations.
我們從未離開過
We never left.
所以...
So...
我打造了這些能隔墻觀看的特別之地
I had these special places where I could look through the walls
來觀察他們
watch them.
特別之地
Special places.
錄像時代就這么到來
Then the video age came
接著你又升級了你的小愛好  對嗎
and you upgraded your little hobby, right?
那真的很酷
That was pretty cool, too.
尤其是當旅館每況愈下時  你知道嗎
I mean, especially when the motel kind of went downhill, you know?
各種各樣瘋狂的事接踵而至
That brought all kinds of crazy stuff.
那些超贊的妓女  那些酒鬼
The crack whores, drunk dudes,
打自己的老婆  他們
beating their wives, they...
相信我  這可是場表演
That is a show, believe me.
但是這些也逐漸變得無趣
But even that got a little old and dull,
所以你就給房客噴藥來增添樂趣
so you spiced it up by dosing people with drugs?
幾個月前
A few months ago,
我在第三大街看到一個服用了迷幻藥的人
I saw this guy out on Third, tripping on acid.
感覺他就像瘋了一樣
He was, like, out of his mind,
真是太...
and it was just so...
太奇怪了
so weird.
我就是那時想到給浴室裝那個噴霧器的
And that is when I came up with that rig for the bathroom.
你必須得承認  這相當聰明
You have to admit... it is pretty clever.
真聰明
Clever.
有五個人死了  還有個在醫院
Five people are dead, one is in the hospital.
我只是把油灑在了車上
Hey, I just put the gas in the car... okay?
是他們自己撞上的
They're the ones that crashed it.
老兄
Come on...
你拿到我的帶子了  你也看到了
you've got my tapes. You've seen 'em.
第一個家伙  把自己退剁下來那個
That first dude, hacking his legs off.
還有那個老師  還有那個流浪漢
Or that teacher... oh, and the homeless guy.
他本來就邋里邋遢
I mean, the dude is already a total mess,
收留他的那位女士又帶那么多玩偶
and then the lady has all those dolls!
這是送上門來的一份大禮啊
I mean, that was a gift.
還有那個可憐的墨西哥人
Or the poor Mexican guy...
殺了自己的老婆
killing his wife.
說實話  我不知道他會那么做
Honestly, I didn't see that coming.
那件事...
I mean, that...
真是...
that...
真是太棒了
...that was awesome.
太棒了
Awesome.
你為什么這么看著我
What are you looking at me like that for?
大家每天上網看的東西
Come on, people go online every day to look at stuff
不就是這樣的么
that's just like that.
但你操縱了這一切
But you manipulated this.
是你讓這些事發生
You made this happen.
是你讓那些人  那些無辜的人
You made these people, these innocent people,
做這些事
do these things.
那又怎樣
So what?
有什么區別嗎
What's the difference?
你有二十五年的時間來想想有什么區別
Well, you'll have 25 years to life to figure that out.
不過  你得呆在一個小房間
And the weird thing is you're gonna be in a little room
還有人每天二十四小時看著你
with people watching you 24/7.
我聽說你很快就可以出院了
I, uh, heard they're going to be discharging you soon.
是的
Yeah.
我覺得我已經好得差不多了
I guess I've healed as much as I'm going to.
我  我過來是想告訴你
Well, I... I came 'cause I wanted you to know
我們已經抓到了那個應該為發生在
that we arrested the man responsible
你和你妻子身上的事負責的人
for what happened to you and to your wife.
他沒有親手殺人
He didn't physically do the killings,
但事情是他一手造成的
but he is responsible.
不好意思  我有點糊涂了
Well, I-I... I'm sorry, I'm a little confused here.
我們逮捕的那個人
The man we arrested...
住在旅館里
lived in the motel,
給他的幾個房客下了藥
and he drugged several of his guests.
那天晚上  你妻子睡覺的時候
That night, when your wife went to sleep,
你進了浴室偷著抽了根煙
you went into the bathroom and you snuck a cigarette.
當你在浴室的時候
While you were in the bathroom,
你被噴了一種強勁的致幻藥
you were dosed with a very potent psychedelic drug,
導致你在性格和行為上大變
and it caused a violent change in your personality and your behavior.
你看到的...那張臉
That face... that you saw...
襲擊你妻子的那個人
the man who was hitting your wife...
過一會兒
Uh... in a little while,
警察會過來
there's going to be some police officers coming here,
你得跟他們走一趟  好嗎
and you're going to need to go with them, okay?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我想為我不是"我"的時候說過的話道歉
I want to apologize for anything I may have said while I wasn't myself.
那其實都不是你自己的話或者行為
It wasn't your words so much as your actions, really.
很顯然
And, obviously...
我也為我的行為道歉
I apologize for those, too.
接受我的道歉嗎
Apology accepted?
是的
Yes.
接受道歉
Apology accepted.
那就好
Good.
那你應該不會想著報復我了吧
Then you won't be trying to get back at me in some way?
當然不會
No, of course not.
但是換了我的話  我就不會喝那杯咖啡
But I wouldn't drink that coffee, if I were you.